

Contact

- 0909-041-3921
- jerimieclaor19@gmail.com
- jerimie.escorido.yahoo.com
- 325 Purok 3 Sampaloc, San Rafael, Bulacan

About Me

A responsible and challenging entry level work that will utilize my education background. To gain work experience knowledge, and capabilities of good working and learning new skills that will develop my professional abilities.

Refrences

Mrs. Susana Martin

Business Woman 0909-041-3921

Jerimie E. Claor

Information Technology

Education

Tertiary

2019 - 2023 | Baliwag Polytechnic College

· Bachelor of Science Information Technology

Secondary

2011 - 2015 | San Rafael National Trade School

Primary

2006 - 2011 | Sampaloc Elementary School

Work Experience

Waiter

2016 - 2017 | Buffet

Staff

2017 - 2018 | Lemon Shaker

Service Crew

2018 - 2019 | Mcdonald's

Skills

Microsoft Office (Word and Presentation)

HTML CSS, and JavaScript Programming (Front-End)

Can use basic C++ programming languages

Qualifications

Positive thinker, honest

Eagerness to learn and committed to work

Can work and collaborate in organization